WOLOWITZ:
Heads up! Watch out!
(Leonard:)Are you mad at me?
(Penny:)No, stop being stupid.
(Leonard:)Um... whew?
(Leonard:)Is this about the test,
or is this about us?
(Penny:)Look, I don't need
a score on a test
(Penny:)to make me worry about something
I'm already worried about.
(Leonard:)What are you
worried about?
(scoffs)
(Penny:)That we're engaged and
have nothing in common,
(Penny:)and it scares me.
(Leonard:)Yeah, that scares me, too.
(Penny:)It does?
(Leonard:)Sometimes.
Well, that's not good!
(Penny:)You being blindly infatuated
with me was the rock
(Penny:)we were building
this relationship on!
(Leonard:)Okay, well, this might
make you feel better.
(Leonard:)Uh, we're both scared that
our marriage will be a disaster,
(Leonard:)and so, that's something
that we have in common.